<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
xmlns:rawvoice="http://www.rawvoice.com/rawvoiceRssModule/"
xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0"
>

<channel>
	<title>MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com</link>
	<description>Starting An Online Store So Your Spouse Can Quit And Stay At Home With The Kids</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:24:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.3.2</generator>
<!-- podcast_generator="Blubrry PowerPress/8.4.8" mode="advanced" feedslug="feed" Blubrry PowerPress Podcasting plugin for WordPress (https://www.blubrry.com/powerpress/) -->
	<atom:link rel="hub" href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" />
	<itunes:summary>A podcast about entrepreneurs who quit their jobs to start successful online businesses.  Through a series of personal interviews, Steve extracts the little details and the exact strategies that contributed to their success.  All of the entrepreneurs featured on the show bootstrapped their businesses from the ground up and hustled their way to the top without risking their life savings, without sacrificing their relationships by working 100 hour weeks and without needing extensive technical knowledge.  There is no fluff and every episode is packed with actionable takeaways.</itunes:summary>
	<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
	<itunes:explicit>clean</itunes:explicit>
	<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
	<itunes:owner>
		<itunes:name>Steve Chou</itunes:name>
		<itunes:email>mywifequitherjob@gmail.com</itunes:email>
	</itunes:owner>
	<managingEditor>mywifequitherjob@gmail.com (Steve Chou)</managingEditor>
	<itunes:subtitle>Steve Chou from the MyWifeQuitHerJob Blog discusses ecommerce, online business, marketing and selling on Amazon.  Special interviews with experts like Pat Flynn, Ryan Daniel Moran, Amy Porterfield, Scott Voelker and Andrew Warner of Mixergy</itunes:subtitle>
	<image>
		<title>MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</title>
		<url>https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3-168.jpg</url>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/category/podcast/</link>
	</image>
	<itunes:category text="Business" />
	<googleplay:category text="Business"/>
	<itunes:category text="Business">
		<itunes:category text="Marketing" />
	</itunes:category>
	<itunes:category text="Business">
		<itunes:category text="Entrepreneurship" />
	</itunes:category>
	<item>
		<title>360: Idiotic Mistakes We&#8217;ve All Made As Ecommerce Entrepreneurs With Kurt Elster</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode360/</link>
				<comments>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode360/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The My Wife Quit Her Job Podcast With Steve Chou]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=69144</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Today I have my friend Kurt Elster back on the show. Kurt runs the Unofficial Shopify Podcast which is one of the few e-commerce podcasts that I listen to. In this episode, both Kurt and I discuss the 6 most common mistakes that we&#8217;ve all made as ecommerce entrepreneurs. We talk about the stuff that almost everyone gets wrong when first starting out including myself! What You&#8217;ll Learn Steve&#8217;s list of boneheaded mistakes Kurt&#8217;s running list of blunders How to avoid making these same mistakes with your store Other Resources And Books Unofficial Shopify Podcast Sponsors Postscript.io &#8211; Postscript.io is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode360/">360: Idiotic Mistakes We&#8217;ve All Made As Ecommerce Entrepreneurs With Kurt Elster</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<wfw:commentRss>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode360/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
				<enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/mywifequitherjob/MWQHJ360KurtElster_1.mp3" length="65867208" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:subtitle>Today I have my friend Kurt Elster back on the show. Kurt runs the Unofficial Shopify Podcast which is one of the few e-commerce podcasts that I listen to.  - In this episode, both Kurt and I discuss the 6 most common mistakes that we&#039;ve all made as e...</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Today I have my friend Kurt Elster back on the show. Kurt runs the Unofficial Shopify Podcast which is one of the few e-commerce podcasts that I listen to. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In this episode, both Kurt and I discuss the 6 most common mistakes that we&#039;ve all made as ecommerce entrepreneurs.  We talk about the stuff that almost everyone gets wrong when first starting out including myself!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
		<itunes:duration>54:38</itunes:duration>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is Alibaba Legit And Safe? How To Avoid Getting Ripped Off</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/is-alibaba-legit/</link>
				<comments>https://mywifequitherjob.com/is-alibaba-legit/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Store]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Sourcing]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=69076</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Alibaba is one of the best platforms to find suppliers for your ecommerce business. But is Alibaba legit and safe to buy from? The short answer is yes! But you must understand how to use Alibaba correctly and do your own due diligence in order to find a quality supplier without getting ripped off. In other words, you can&#8217;t just haphazardly perform supplier searches on Alibaba and expect to get good results. In this step by step guide, you&#8217;ll learn how to avoid Alibaba scams, middlemen and outright fraud on the platform! What Is Alibaba And How Does It Work? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/is-alibaba-legit/">Is Alibaba Legit And Safe? How To Avoid Getting Ripped Off</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<wfw:commentRss>https://mywifequitherjob.com/is-alibaba-legit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>359: A Deep Dive Into Content Marketing Today With Corbett Barr</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode359/</link>
				<comments>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode359/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 22:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blogging]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The My Wife Quit Her Job Podcast With Steve Chou]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=69039</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Today I&#8217;m thrilled to have Corbett Barr back on the show. For all of you who don&#8217;t remember Corbett from episode 45, he used to run a VC funded start-up, got totally burned out, and then decided start a business that suited his lifestyle. He&#8217;s started many successful blogs and an incredible online business program called Fizzle which he has been running for almost a decade now. In this episode, we&#8217;re going to talk about the creator economy. What You&#8217;ll Learn How Corbett started Fizzle.co Why creators rule the world today Which content medium is the best to start, a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode359/">359: A Deep Dive Into Content Marketing Today With Corbett Barr</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<wfw:commentRss>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode359/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
				<enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/mywifequitherjob/MWQHJ359CorbettBarr.mp3" length="61565364" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:subtitle>Today I&#039;m thrilled to have Corbett Barr back on the show. For all of you who don&#039;t remember Corbett from episode 45, he used to run a VC funded start-up, got totally burned out, and then decided start a business that suited his lifestyle.  - </itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Today I&#039;m thrilled to have Corbett Barr back on the show. For all of you who don&#039;t remember Corbett from episode 45, he used to run a VC funded start-up, got totally burned out, and then decided start a business that suited his lifestyle. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
He&#039;s started many successful blogs and an incredible online business program called Fizzle which he has been running for almost a decade now.   In this episode, we&#039;re going to talk about the creator economy.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
		<itunes:duration>51:03</itunes:duration>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helium 10 Vs Jungle Scout &#8211; The Best Amazon Seller Tools For 2021</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/helium10-vs-junglescout/</link>
				<comments>https://mywifequitherjob.com/helium10-vs-junglescout/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 17:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Store]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68850</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Helium 10 vs Jungle Scout. Which Amazon seller tool is the best for you? This post will break down and compare the 2 most popular Amazon tools from the perspective of a 7 figure ecommerce business owner who has used both services. In order to be successful selling on Amazon today, you absolutely need to use an Amazon seller tool. Otherwise, you&#8217;ll be at a severe disadvantage compared to other FBA sellers. Over the years, there have been many different players in the Amazon software space but the industry has consolidated to just a few companies offering all in one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/helium10-vs-junglescout/">Helium 10 Vs Jungle Scout &#8211; The Best Amazon Seller Tools For 2021</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<wfw:commentRss>https://mywifequitherjob.com/helium10-vs-junglescout/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>358: The Ultimate Website Audit Checklist With Ian Cleary</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode358/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 06:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[SEO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The My Wife Quit Her Job Podcast With Steve Chou]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68897</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, I&#8217;m happy to have Ian Cleary on the show. Ian runs RazorSocial where he helps companies with their digital marketing efforts, and today we&#8217;re going to talk about website design, content marketing, and how to do a full audit of your site for SEO and conversions. If you own a website of any kind, then this episode will improve your online sales! What You&#8217;ll Learn Why Ian started RazorSocial Ian&#8217;s ultimate website audit checklist Common mistakes that most webmasters make Other Resources And Books RazorSocial.com Sponsors Postscript.io &#8211; Postscript.io is the SMS marketing platform that I personally use for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode358/">358: The Ultimate Website Audit Checklist With Ian Cleary</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/mywifequitherjob/MWQHJ358IanCleary.mp3" length="55228056" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:subtitle>Today, I&#039;m happy to have Ian Cleary on the show.  - Ian runs RazorSocial where he helps companies with their digital marketing efforts, and today we&#039;re going to talk about website design, content marketing,</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Today, I&#039;m happy to have Ian Cleary on the show. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Ian runs RazorSocial where he helps companies with their digital marketing efforts, and today we&#039;re going to talk about website design, content marketing, and how to do a full audit of your site for SEO and conversions.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
If you own a website of any kind, then this episode will improve your online sales!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
		<itunes:duration>45:46</itunes:duration>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Businesses Should Avoid Stripe Payments.  Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/stripe-sucks/</link>
				<comments>https://mywifequitherjob.com/stripe-sucks/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 17:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Store]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68860</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>In this post, you&#8217;ll learn why you should avoid Stripe payments to process credit cards for your online business. Here&#8217;s my story. First off, I want to come out and say that I love Stripe as a product. Their signup process is easy and they have the best credit card processing API in the industry. Most applications support Stripe out of the box and they provide libraries for geeks like me who like to code custom functionality into their websites. Compared to other payment processors that I&#8217;ve worked with, I can wholeheartedly say that my experience with Stripe has been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/stripe-sucks/">Businesses Should Avoid Stripe Payments.  Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<wfw:commentRss>https://mywifequitherjob.com/stripe-sucks/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>357: When To Shut Down Your Business Or Quit Your Job With Steve Chou</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode357/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 02:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Productivity/Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The My Wife Quit Her Job Podcast With Steve Chou]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68853</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Today, I’m doing a solo episode to answer yet another question that I get asked all the time. Steve, how do you know when to quit your job? How do you know when to move on from your business? Well here’s my exact framework. Make sure you have a pen and paper handy before listening and please let me know what you think. Would love to know your score! What You&#8217;ll Learn 8 questions to ask yourself before quitting anything When to give up and when to suck it up How to shut down your business without any regrets Other [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode357/">357: When To Shut Down Your Business Or Quit Your Job With Steve Chou</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/mywifequitherjob/MWQHJ357SteveQuitting.mp3" length="37193857" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:subtitle>Today, I’m doing a solo episode to answer yet another question that I get asked all the time.   - Steve, how do you know when to quit your job? How do you know when to move on from your business?   - Well here’s my exact framework.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Today, I’m doing a solo episode to answer yet another question that I get asked all the time.  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Steve, how do you know when to quit your job? How do you know when to move on from your business?  &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Well here’s my exact framework.  Make sure you have a pen and paper handy before listening and please let me know what you think. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Would love to know your score!</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
		<itunes:duration>19:13</itunes:duration>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Automation &#8211; How To Run Your Ecommerce Business On Autopilot</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/amazon-automation/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Store]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68727</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>In this post, you&#8217;ll learn how to apply Amazon automation, computers and software to systematize practically every aspect of your ecommerce business. Running a successful Amazon business involves managing many moving parts. For example, you must maintain your inventory levels, adjust your pricing, respond to customer inquiries, tweak your advertising and manage your reputation. Meanwhile, there are malicious sellers constantly trying to hijack your listings and knock off your products. New competitors pop up daily and it&#8217;s a cutthroat environment. To make things worse, you also have to worry about Amazon suspending your listings or outright copying and private labeling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/amazon-automation/">Amazon Automation &#8211; How To Run Your Ecommerce Business On Autopilot</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
									</item>
		<item>
		<title>356: The Right Way To Setup Your Website Analytics With Chris Mercer</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode356/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 02:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Ecommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The My Wife Quit Her Job Podcast With Steve Chou]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=68769</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Today I have my friend Chris Mercer on the show. Chris is the founder of MeasurementMarketing.io and he specializes in website analytics. Analytics may not sound like the sexiest of topics but most people are doing it wrong. Most people don&#8217;t know how to use Google Analytics and most shop owners have no idea what metrics to focus on. In this episode, Chris teaches us the right way to gather and analyze your data for an e-commerce store. What You&#8217;ll Learn Chris&#8217;s backstory and why he decided to specialize in analytics The right way to setup Google Analytics for your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/episode356/">356: The Right Way To Setup Your Website Analytics With Chris Mercer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
						<enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/mywifequitherjob/MWQHJ356ChrisMercer.mp3" length="70131437" type="audio/mpeg" />
			<itunes:subtitle>Today I have my friend Chris Mercer on the show.  Chris is the founder of MeasurementMarketing.io and he specializes in website analytics. - Analytics may not sound like the sexiest of topics but most people are doing it wrong.</itunes:subtitle>
		<itunes:summary>Today I have my friend Chris Mercer on the show.  Chris is the founder of MeasurementMarketing.io and he specializes in website analytics.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Analytics may not sound like the sexiest of topics but most people are doing it wrong. Most people don&#039;t know how to use Google Analytics and most shop owners have no idea what metrics to focus on. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In this episode, Chris teaches us the right way to gather and analyze your data for an e-commerce store.</itunes:summary>
		<itunes:author>Steve Chou</itunes:author>
		<itunes:image href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/powerpress/PodcastImageV3.jpg" />
		<itunes:duration>58:12</itunes:duration>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Influencer Program &#8211; How It Works And The Juicy Details</title>
		<link>https://mywifequitherjob.com/amazon-influencer-program/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Steve Chou]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Amazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How to Build an Online Store]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mywifequitherjob.com/?p=67950</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;ve built up a large social media following or a substantial YouTube subscriber base and you don&#8217;t currently have a website, then the Amazon Influencer Program is a great way for you to monetize your audience. As an aspiring Instagram or YouTube influencer, you may not have your own branded website yet. After all, if your audience primarily lives on a 3rd party platform like YouTube or Instagram, why spend the time and money putting up a polished website that gets very little traffic? But let&#8217;s say that you promote a wide variety of affiliate products through your social [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com/amazon-influencer-program/">Amazon Influencer Program &#8211; How It Works And The Juicy Details</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mywifequitherjob.com">MyWifeQuitHerJob.com</a>.</p>
]]></description>
									</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
